Now before we finish up with our navigator section,
在完成导航器部分之前
there are just a few small changes that we need to make.
我们还需要进行几项小的更改
If you remember back to our AddEntry component that we made,
在我们构建的 AddEntry 组件中
we have these sections right here.
我们预留了这些注释部分
Navigate to home and Route to home.
即 Navigate to Home 和 Route to Home
So what we want to do, is whenever we submit a new day basically,
每当我们提交新的日期信息
or whenever we reset the current day,
或重置当天信息
what we want to do is all of these things as well,
我们想要执行所有这些操作
as navigate back to the home screen.
并且返回主屏幕
So the way that we need to do that in this file,
我们将在此文件中
is with this method called NavigationActions,
使用方法 NavigationActions
which is coming from the React Navigation package.
来自于 react-navigation 软件包
And the way we can do this,
实现方法是
is let's go ahead and down here,
转到这里
make a new method, we'll call it toHome.
新建一个方法 叫做 toHome
And what this is going to do,
它将
is it's going to call,
调用
this.props.navigation.dispatch, so it's similar to Redux.
this.props.navigation.dispatch 类似于 Redux
And what we are going to dispatch, is NavigationsActions.back.
我们将分派 NavigationsActions.back
So we want to go back,
我们想回到某个地方
and where we want to go back from,
我们从哪里回去呢？
is the route that has the key of AddEntry.
也就是具有 key“AddEntry”的位置
So we want to basically, go from where we are,
我们想从当前所在的位置
back to where we previously were.
回到之前的位置
And so now what we can do is right here,
我们可以在这里
we can say, this.toHome.
输入 this.toHome
And here, we can say this.toHome as well.
在这里也输入 this.toHome
Now, you'll notice here that we're not
你会发现
really worrying too much about the order of the way things happen.
我们并没太关心事情的发生顺序
You could get kind of picky about that,
你可以对顺序比较严格
I'm not going to worry about it,
但是我不太在意
but if you want to, by all means feel free to.
如果你想遵守一定的顺序 完全可以这么做
What I mean by that is, we're dispatching,
我们的顺序是 分派
we're setting state, this is all kind of asynchronous,
设置状态 相当于异步状态
so it's all just going to happen.
一切都会发生 并且可行。
But it works fine. But if you want to refactor it by yourself, by all means go ahead.
如果你想重构执行顺序 完全可以
So now let's go ahead and check at entry.
现在转到 Add Entry
So let's just enter in some information for the day. That looks great.
输入这一天的一些信息 看起来不错
When we add a new entry,
当我们添加新的条目后
we get taken to our home view that shows this.
转到显示这些信息的主屏幕
And now what should happen, is when we reset,
现在当我们点击 RESET
we also get taken back to the home view,
也会回到主屏幕
and then it says, "Hey,
并提示
don't forget to log your data for today!"
嘿 别忘了记录今天的数据
Because we just cleared that.
因为我们刚刚清空了数据